hello my name is daniela i would like to
invite you to join a live web stream on
the topic of regenerative economies for
regenerative cultures this will take
place on thursday the 2nd of april at 3
p.m.
lisbon time and 4 p.m. madrid time or
central european time
the talk will explore how important now
in this new context of a global viral
pandemic it is to rapidly strengthen
community resilience and bio regional
capacity for people in place to meet
their primary needs in a regenerative
way and in a restorative way in the
region they inhabit I look forward to
sharing these ideas with you and then
having a question-and-answer session
with anybody who wants to join and the
beautiful thing now is that rather than
giving this talk at Cotto jest in a
culture center in the center of Lisbon
to a few hundred people I have an
opportunity to give it to as many people
as want to join us on Thursday at 3 p.m.
Lisbon time Thursday the 2nd of April
the regenerative economies for
regenerative cultures is the topic so
come and join us thank you bye